eguide.com.my 2008-09-12

# eGuide - (Malaysia) eGuide Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us and is taken seriously. This Privacy Statement covers how we at eGuide treat personal information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number. If you have voluntarily provided information and unless otherwise informed by you, we will deem that you have consented to the collection and use of your personally identifiable information as described in this Privacy Statement. 

If you are only browsing the Website, we do not capture data that allows us to identify you individually. 

We collect personal information when you contact us, register with us or where you are required to enter any of the mentioned personally identifiable information like your email address or name, and when you take part in any promotions or contests conducted through eGuide. This is in order that we can serve you in a more efficient and effective way, unless such sharing is prohibited by legislation. For your convenience, we may also display to you data you had previously supplied us. This will speed up the transaction and save you the trouble of repeating previous submissions. Should the data be out-of-date, please supply us the latest data. 

We have put in place reasonably adequate safeguards to protect information that we have collected about you. We limit access to personal information about you to employees whom we reasonably believe need to have access to in order to do their jobs. 

We do not rent, sell or share personal information about you with third parties, save for affiliated companies and trusted business partners. However, we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to eGuide services and products, announcements, promotions, contests or newsletters. If you do not wish to receive such offers or mailings, you can easily choose to unsubscribe from the received publications. 

In the event that we do share such collected information in accordance with this Privacy Statement, the disclosure will be limited to only aggregated information which will not identify you. Recipients of such information will also be restricted to using the information for the purpose for which it was disclosed and for no other unauthorized purposes. 

This site may contain links to websites whose data protection and privacy practices may differ from ours. We are not responsible for the content and privacy practices of these other websites and encourage you to consult the privacy notices of those sites. 

We reserve the right to update this Privacy Statement from time to time as we expand our services and products
